Finding Aid to the Nancy Stoller Papers, 1981-1995 MSS 2000-6
University of California, San Francisco Archives & Special Collections
- Organizations, 1984-1995; Series 2; 263 Folders: Cartons 3-7 Folders 3/1-7/14
  - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF), 1985-1994; Subseries 2.3; 66 Folders: Carton 4 Folders 4/35-4/71; Carton 5 Folders 5/1-5/29
    - Intravenous Drug Users (IVDU) (Carton 5, Folder 4-29)
      - Samuel R. Friedman and Cathy Casriel - "Drug Users' Organizations and AIDS Policy", circa 1986 (Carton 5, Folder 27)
      - Gerald Friedland - "Intravenous Drug Abusers and the Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome (AIDS)", August 1985 (Carton 5, Folder 28)
      - Don CIRCA Des Jarlais and Samuel R. Friedman - "Prevention Policy Questions for AIDS among Intravenous Drug Users", November 1985 (Carton 5, Folder 29)
  - California Prostitutes Education Project (CAL-PEP), 1988-1996; Subseries 2.4; 21 Folders: Carton 5 Folders 5/30-5/50
    This subseries contains materials documenting the work of the CAL-PEP, an AIDS prevention program organized and run by prostitutes and former prostitutes. It also includes some COYOTE (Call Off Your Old Tired Ethics) materials. Besides minutes and other program and grant related materials, there are some materials connected with a controversy that arose around Gloria Lockett, the organization's executive director, and her hiring and management policies. Of special interest are the interview with Lockett from 1993, clippings about the controversy, the "NIDA Grant" folder which discusses an earlier difference of opinion between CAL-PEP and two other organizations. Also included is draft of Stoller's 1993 paper, "Post-Modern Prostitutes: When Sex Workers Run AIDS Organizations," which she had presented at a conference and correspondence concerning the best way to inform Lockett about the paper. Also of interest is a draft of "Prostitutes Prevent AIDS: A Handbook for Health Educators" from 1988.
    - COYOTE (Carton 5, Folder 30-31)
      - 1985-1987 (Carton 5, Folder 30)
      - Sex as Sin to Sex as Work: COYOTE and the Reorganization of Prostitution as a Social Problem, Valerie Jenness, 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 31)
    - Board of Director's Minutes, October 25, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 32)
    - Grant Application: Evaluation of CAL-PEP Mobile Van Prevention Program, 1995 (Carton 5, Folder 33)
    - Fax Sheets [Grant related], 1995-1996 (Carton 5, Folder 34)
    - Interview with Gloria Lockett, 1993 (Carton 5, Folder 35)
    - Clippings (Concerning Washington and Lockett/ CAL-PEP controversy), 1993 (Carton 5, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence and Conference Paper - "Post-Modern Prostitutes: When Sex Workers Run AIDS Organizations", 1993 (Carton 5, Folder 37)
    - Grant Application to East Oakland Healthy Start, 1992 (Carton 5, Folder 38)
    - NIDA Grant - Conflict with AWARE, and Board Meetings, 1990-1991 (Carton 5, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Communications, 1988-1990 (Carton 5, Folder 40)
    - CDC Proposal (draft), 1989 (Carton 5, Folder 41)
    - By-laws, Employee Manual and Board of Directors List, circa 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 42)
    - Finances, 1988; 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 43)
    - "Office of AIDS Progress Report: Second Quarter Report", 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 44)
    - Notes, 1989 (Carton 5, Folder 45)
    - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 46)
    - Communications (including job description and personnel policy), 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 47)
    - Project HAAND (draft), 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 48)
    - "Miscellaneous", 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 49)
    - "Prostitutes Prevent AIDS: A Handbook for Health Educators" (draft), 1988 (Carton 5, Folder 50)
  - ACT-UP New York City, 1988-1994; Subseries 2.5; 33 Folders: Carton 5 Folders 5/51-5/63; Carton 6 Folders 6/1-6/20
    This subseries contains materials on Stoller's more formal "participant-observer" research with ACT-UP New York City in 1992. Of special interest are the two notebooks from her time with ACT-UP. These two small notebooks: blue (ACT-UP New York demonstrations) and pink (Meetings/interviews - 1989) are some of the raw data that went into her study of the organization.
    In addition to the material from her winter 1989 stay in New York, there are also selected materials from 1990 and 1992, mainly minutes and other materials from the chapter's weekly meetings. The earliest and latest materials in this subseries are newspaper and magazine articles from 1988 and 1994. Also of special interest is the Women's Caucus - Women and AIDS Handbook from March 1988.
    - Observation Journals [small notebooks], 1989 (Carton 5, Folder 51)
    - April 13th Meeting, 1992 (Carton 5, Folder 52)
    - March 23rd and 30th Meeting Materials, 1992 (Carton 5, Folder 53)
    - March 16th Meeting (includes transcript of meeting), 1992 (Carton 5, Folder 54)
    - Materials from March 16th Meeting, 1992 (Carton 5, Folder 55)
    - Other ACT-UP Chapters and other organizations, 1992 (Carton 5, Folder 56)
    - July 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 57)
    - June 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 58)
    - May 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 59)
    - April 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 60)
    - March 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 61)
    - February 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 62)
    - January 1990 (Carton 5, Folder 63)
    - December 4th Meeting, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 1)
    - St. Patrick's Cathedral Protest, December 10, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 2)
    - December Flyers, Articles, Magazines, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 3)
    - December Newspaper Clippings, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 4)
    - November 13th Weekly Report, et al., 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 5)
    - November General - Flyers, 3 Outweek Magazines and articles, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 6)
    - October 2nd Meeting, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 7)
    - October 9th Meeting - Weekly Report and handouts, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 8)
    - October 16th Meeting - Weekly Report and handouts, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 9)
    - October 23rd Meeting - Weekly Report and handouts, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 10)
    - October 30th Meeting - handouts, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 11)
    - October General - including 3 Outweek Magazines, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 12)
    - October Newspaper Clippings (two copies of the September/October issue of ACT-UP Reports), 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 13)
    - September - includes an Outweek Magazine, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 14)
    - August 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 15)
    - July 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 16)
    - June 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 17)
    - ACT UP Women's Caucus - Women and AIDS Handbook, March 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 18)
    - Outlook and newspaper clippings, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 19)
    - New York Times clippings and Advocate and Gay Community News Articles List, 1989; 1994 (Carton 6, Folder 20)
  - Women's Organizations, 1985-1998; Subseries 2.6; 41 Folders: Carton 6 Folders 6/21-6/47; Carton 7 Folders 7/1-7/14
    This subseries contains materials on several organizations concerned with women and AIDS, most specifically the Women's AIDS Network (WAN), which was affiliated to some extent with the San Francisco AIDS Foundation (SFAF); the Women & AIDS Risk Network (WARN), which was an outreach project of the California School of Professional Psychology (CSPP) funded by the National Institute on Drug Abuse[NIDA] for three years [12/87-10/90]; and WORLD (Women Organized to Respond to Life-threatening Diseases), a newsletter full of personal stories of HIV+ Women. Also included is an undated statement on AIDS from the California branch of the National Organization For Women (NOW) and single folders of information from several regional groups including: Long Beach, California; Boulder, Colorado; Boston, Massachusetts; the Washington, D.CIRCA and Maryland area; Portland, Oregon, and even England. The Portland, Oregon folder includes pamphlets and material on 1987 conference "Love Carefully ... Stop AIDS: A Free Conference for Women". The condom and button from this folder have been moved to the Ephemera Series.
    - WAN (Women's AIDS Network) (Carton 6, Folder 21-41)
      - Bylaws - Original and Updated, 1988; 1991 (Carton 6, Folder 21)
      - Women at Risk: Strategies for AIDS Prevention and Education Conference, November 16, 1984 (Carton 6, Folder 22)
      - Meeting Minutes and other materials, 1985-1986 (Carton 6, Folder 23)
      - To Health Commissioner, 1986 (Carton 6, Folder 24)
      - Media Guide [From SFAF], 1986 (Carton 6, Folder 25)
      - Meeting Minutes and other materials, 1987 (Carton 6, Folder 26)
      - Announcements, Communications, 1987 (Carton 6, Folder 27)
      - Meeting Minutes (including Jan 30th Retreat & Board Election Materials), 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 28)
      - Announcements, Communications, Notes, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 29)
      - Community Coalitions, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 30)
      - Hearst/Hulley Article and Response, April 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 31)
      - Ann Meredith/"Until That Last Breath" Photography Exhibit, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 32)
      - Meeting Minutes and other documents, 1989 (Carton 6, Folder 33)
      - Meeting Minutes and other correspondence, 1990 (Carton 6, Folder 34)
      - Other Documents, 1990 (Carton 6, Folder 35)
      - Fundraising and Grant Proposals, 1990 (Carton 6, Folder 36)
      - Meeting Minutes and other documents, 1991 (Carton 6, Folder 37)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Carton 6, Folder 38)
      - Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Carton 6, Folder 39)
      - Meeting Minutes/Newsletters, 1994 (Carton 6, Folder 40)
      - Newsletters and Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Carton 6, Folder 41)
    - WARN (Women and AIDS Risk Network), Carton 6 Folder 42 - Carton 7 folder 5
      - CSPP (California School of Professional Psychology)/WARN Training Plan, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 42)
      - Summary of Project, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 43)
      - Research Team, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 44)
      - Ethnographic Training Handouts, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 45)
      - Demographic and Population Estimates [Los Angeles], 1980-1988 (Carton 6, Folder 46)
      - Background Information, 1988 (Carton 6, Folder 47)
      - Ethnographic Reports - Cathy, 1988 (Carton 7, Folder 1)
      - Ethnographic Reports - Regina, 1988 (Carton 7, Folder 2)
      - Travel and Business, 1988 (Carton 7, Folder 3)
      - Notes, 1988 (Carton 7, Folder 4)
      - Communications, 1989-1990 (Carton 7, Folder 5)
    - WORLD (Women Organized to Respond to Life-threatening Diseases) Magazine, 1994-1995 (Carton 7, Folder 6)
    - NOW (National Organization for Women) California, undated (Carton 7, Folder 7)
    - Long Beach Study - Lesbians and AIDS, Cathy Reback, 1989 (Carton 7, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles - The Women's AIDS Project, 1986; undated (Carton 7, Folder 9)
    - Boulder, Colorado, 1985 (Carton 7, Folder 10)
    - Boston, Massachusetts, 1986-1988 (Carton 7, Folder 11)
    - Washington, D.CIRCA and Maryland, 1986 (Carton 7, Folder 12)
    - Portland, Oregon — Condom and Button moved to Ephemera, 1985-1987 (Carton 7, Folder 13)
    - England, undated (Carton 7, Folder 14)
- Writings, 1987-1996; Series 3; 39 Folders: Carton 7 Folders 7/15-7/49; Carton 8 Folders 8/1-8/4
  This series consists primarily of drafts and background materials for Stoller's 1998 book Lessons From the Damned. These files are arranged by chapter and/or subject and were kept separately from the other subject files by Stoller. Also in this series are other writings by Stoller, and materials concerning Women Resisting AIDS: Feminist Strategies of Empowerment, eds. Schneider & Stoller, Temple University Press, 1995. The Lessons From the Damned material is arranged by chapter &/or topic and material on each chapter includes drafts of the chapter along with assorted articles, clippings, and other research materials that Stoller had pulled together as reference for that chapter. Some of these materials may also be found elsewhere in the collection, primarily in the subject or organizational files. The first folder contains correspondence concerning the book. The final few folders contain miscellaneous examples of Stoller's other written work and files concerning the reviewing of books and presentations by Stoller.
  Of special interest are interviews with Vito Russo (the pages of this interview were not in order, apparently on purpose) and Larry Kramer. The "Syringe Exchange (1987-1995)" folder is also of note since it contains material of both national and international scope.
  - Lessons From the Damned (Carton 7, Folder 15-48)
    - Correspondence, Outline & Preface drafts, 1990-1991 (Carton 7, Folder 15)
    - Final Chapter (Carton 7, Folder 16-18)
      - #1 - American Health Care System (Carton 7, Folder 16)
      - #2 - AIDS Transparencies (Carton 7, Folder 17)
      - #3 (Carton 7, Folder 18)
    - Cal PEP (Carton 7, Folder 19-22)
      - #1, 1994-1996 (Carton 7, Folder 19)
      - Chapter 3, 1994 (Carton 7, Folder 20)
      - Charts - transparencies, undated (Carton 7, Folder 21)
      - "Post-Modern Prostitutes: When Sex Workers Run AIDS Organizations" - Article for the 1993 American Sociological Association (Carton 7, Folder 22)
    - WAN/WORLD (Carton 7, Folder 23-25)
      - Chapter 3: Feminist Praxis, 1995; undated (Carton 7, Folder 23)
      - Chapter 5: Lesbians, 1994-1995 (Carton 7, Folder 24)
      - Talk Given at National Conference on Women and HIV Infection, December 13-14, 1990 (Carton 7, Folder 25)
    - Chapter 2 - SFAF (San Francisco AIDS Foundation), 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 26)
    - Racial Prescriptions (Carton 7, Folder 27-28)
      - and Sexual Permissions, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 27)
      - Backup, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 28)
    - Asians (Carton 7, Folder 29-31)
      - Chapter 4 - Asians, 1994 (Carton 7, Folder 29)
      - Chapter 5 - Asians Becoming Visible - Draft 1, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 30)
      - San Francisco Bay Area, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 31)
    - ACT-UP Chapter (Carton 7, Folder 32-37)
      - - Draft 1, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 32)
      - Chapter Plan and Notes [includes small blue notebook], 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 33)
      - Vito's Interview, 1989 (Carton 7, Folder 34)
      - Larry Kramer, 1989 (Carton 7, Folder 35)
      - Chronology 1987-1992, undated (Carton 7, Folder 36)
      - St. Patrick's Cathedral Demo, 1989 (Carton 7, Folder 37)
    - Needle Exchange (Carton 7, Folder 38-47)
      - - Draft #1 (2 copies with different corrections/annotations), 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 38)
      - Prevention Point, 1989; 1996,; undated (Carton 7, Folder 39)
      - Sheigla Murphy's Presentation Notes, Reports and Interview, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 40)
      - Luis Kenmitzer Interview, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 41)
      - Moher Downing Interview, 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 42)
      - Prevention Point - Miscellaneous, 1988; 1995 (Carton 7, Folder 43)
      - Syringe Exchange, 1987-1995 (Carton 7, Folder 44)
      - "Drug Policy in the Time of AIDS: The Development of Outreach in San Francisco," Robert S. Broadhead & Eric Margolis in The Sociological Quarterly, 1993 (Carton 7, Folder 45)
      - Various Cities' Experience With Needle Exchange, 1987-1989 (Carton 7, Folder 46)
      - Rally for Needle Exchange and Miscellaneous, 1989-1995 (Carton 7, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous Notes [apparently for book], 1994-1995 (Carton 7, Folder 48)
  - Women Resisting AIDS: Feminist Strategies of Empowerment - Correspondence, Outlines, Drafts, etcetera, 1989-1994 (Carton 7, Folder 49)
  - "Preventing AIDS Among Women: The Role of Community," reprinted from Socialist Review, Fall 1988 (Carton 8, Folder 1)
  - "Creating a Non-Homophobic Atmosphere on Campus.", 1992 (Carton 8, Folder 2)
  - Nancy's Talks and Presentations, undated (Carton 8, Folder 3)
  - Paper Review and Reviewing Papers, 1993 (Carton 8, Folder 4)
- Administrative, Prison, and Non-AIDS Files, 1985-1995; Series 4; 11 Folders: Carton 8 Folders 8/5-8/15
  This series contains materials that don't fit easily into the other categories; many of these files/items came in the second donation/acquisition of this collection. The "AIDS and Prisoners" file contains a cover letter addressed to Urvashi Vaid at the National Prison Project of the ACLU. There are also several files concerning legal actions on behalf of specific prisoners and correspondence to, from, and about prisoners, that are restricted. The material concerning the October 8, 1985, AIDS Update for Health Care Practitioners in the California Department of Corrections, conference, which was sponsored by SFAF, Sacramento AIDS Foundation, and the California Department of Corrections, should be of special interest. The primary non-AIDS files refer to a 1993 Grant Proposal for a Latina Peer Outreach (Breast Cancer) Project in which Stoller was involved. The other files of particular interest include a 1995 file concerning Stoller's promotion to full professor at UCSC, and the final folder in the series which contains a bilingual poem Ligartija/Lizard" by Elba Rosario Sanchez, with an ink drawing by Robert Ciarito.
  - Corrections (Prisons) (Carton 8, Folder 5-10)
    - AIDS and Prisoners, 1985-1988 (Carton 8, Folder 5)
    - Corrections General, 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 6)
    - Incarcerated Parents Manual and letter to Ellen Barry, Legal Services for Prisoners with Children, 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 7)
    - Presentation at the Women's Jail, San Bruno- SFAF, December 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 8)
    - AIDS Update for Health Care Practitioners in the California Department of Corrections (Carton 8, Folder 9-10)
      - Handouts and program, October 8, 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 9)
      - Notes, October 8, 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 10)
  - Non-AIDS Files (Carton 8, Folder 11-15)
    - Non-AIDS Diseases- articles, newsletters, 1987-1990 (Carton 8, Folder 11)
    - Non-AIDS Articles, 1990; undated (Carton 8, Folder 12)
    - Grant Proposal - Latina Peer Outreach (Breast Cancer) Project, 1993 (Carton 8, Folder 13)
    - Promotion File, 1995
    - Poem: "Ligartija/Lizard" by Elba Rosario Sanchez, ink drawing by Robert Ciarito, 1990 (Carton 8, Folder 15)
      - Restricted folders moved to the end of the collection.
- Ephemera, 1983-1995; Series 5; 30 Folders: Carton 8 Folders 8/16-8/44; Container 9 Oversized Folder
  This series includes pamphlets, posters, condoms, buttons, stickers, and other three-dimensional and non-paper items. The pamphlet subseries is quite extensive and includes some pamphlets removed from other parts of the collection. The Ephemera subseries contains a wide variety of materials from the United States and abroad (particularly France and The Netherlands). The poster subseries is also quite broad and international, with older posters from New York City's ADAPT to more recent works, from local posters to South African examples. The poster subseries also contains materials such as oversized flyers, a folded out catalog, and brainstorming sheets from that SFAF "Education Department-Planning" folder. The Portland, Oregon folder in Series II: Organizations, Subseries F: Women's Organizations includes stickers and condoms.
  - Pamphlets, 1983-1994; Subseries 5.1; 18 Folders: Carton Folders 8/16-8/33
    This subseries consists of pamphlets; most are in English but there is also a folder of Spanish language and bilingual pamphlets, as well as a few in French, Tagalog, Chinese, Thai, and Korean. The Bay Area folder includes copies of 2 "fotonovelas," one in English for teens and one in Spanish directed at adults; the Red Cross folder includes a bilingual fotonovela. The National Institutes of Health (NIH) folder contains pamphlets on breast cancer in both English and Spanish. The California folder contains pamphlets from statewide organizations and southern California groups. The majority of non-California material is from Miami, Florida, and the DC/Maryland area. The Federal government folder contains the 1986 Surgeon General's Report, a memo from Pat Christian, and a photocopy of a page from the MMWR.
    - Spanish Language (Some Bilingual), 1983-1992; undated (Carton 8, Folder 16)
    - Asian, Asian-American, and French, 1988-1989; undated (Carton 8, Folder 17)
    - American Indian, 1988; undated (Carton 8, Folder 18)
    - Interfaith & Catholic Organizations, undated (Carton 8, Folder 19)
    - Comic Book Format - SFAF for teens, 1988 (Carton 8, Folder 20)
    - Preservation and Prevention, 1986-1995; undated (Carton 8, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (2 folders), 1983-1984 (Carton 8, Folder 22-23)
    - San Francisco Organizations, 1990; undated (Carton 8, Folder 24)
    - Bay Area, 1988-1989; undated (Carton 8, Folder 25)
    - California, 1986-1990; undated (Carton 8, Folder 26)
    - Columbus, Ohio, 1989-1990 (Carton 8, Folder 27)
    - Other States, 1986-1990; undated (Carton 8, Folder 28)
    - Federal Government, 1984-1992 (Carton 8, Folder 29)
    - Red Cross, 1988-1990 (Carton 8, Folder 30)
    - Commercial and Memberships, 1987-1991 (Carton 8, Folder 31)
    - Educational Programs Associates- Non-AIDS (Breast Cancer and birth control methods), 1986-1994 (Carton 8, Folder 32)
    - National Institutes of Health (NIH) - Breast cancer pamphlets., 1992-1994 (Carton 8, Folder 33)
  - Ephemera/Objects, 1990; 1992,; undated; Subseries 5.2; 11 Folders: Carton 8 Folders 8/34-8/44
    This subseries consists of various three dimensional items, including buttons, stickers, condoms, and dental dams. The most unusual item is a harness for holding a dental dam in place. Audio tapes are also included. Most of the items are not dated.
    - Two Session Tapes from the VIII International Conference on AIDS/III STD World Congress, Amsterdam, The Netherlands (Carton 8, Folder 34-35)
      - Session #41, July 19-24, 1992 (Carton 8, Folder 34)
      - Session #183, July 19-24, 1992 (Carton 8, Folder 35)
    - Good Vibrations Catalog, red leather dental dam harness, 2 dental dams, Dam Guidelines and directions for using the "Dammit" dental dam harness, undated (Carton 8, Folder 36)
    - 4 Buttons - AIDS National Conference on Women and HIV Infection, December 13-14, 1990 (Carton 8, Folder 37)
    - French coaster and small foam figure with receipt and small shopping bag (Carton 8, Folder 38)
    - From The Netherlands - 4 Condoms and 5 Stickers (Carton 8, Folder 39)
    - 2 stickers from the Kuwait Third International Conference on Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome "AIDS" (Carton 8, Folder 40)
    - 3 assorted condoms (Carton 8, Folder 41)
    - 1 condom, 1 button from Portland, Oregon Women & AIDS Conference, 1987 (Carton 8, Folder 42)
    - Sheet of Queer Nation stickers (Carton 8, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous stickers and small paper objects (Carton 8, Folder 44)
    - RESTRICTED - Correspondence to, from, and about Prisoners (w/AIDS), - SFAF - RESTRICTED, 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 45)
    - RESTRICTED - Legal Documents - Compassionate Release Case for Woman Prisoner with Liver Disease, - SFAF - RESTRICTED, 1985 (Carton 8, Folder 46)
  - Posters and Oversized Materials, 1984-1992; undated; Subseries 5.3; Container 9 - 1 oversized folder
    This subseries consists of posters and oversized flyers. Most of the posters are not dated. The posters have been sorted into groups by size and the organization they were issued by. Of special interest are a set of 5 posters from the Township AIDS Project (Johannesburg, South Africa), and an oversized illustrated souvenir map of a Johannesburg shopping district can be found later in the collection. The earliest materials in the subseries appear to be 3 posters from ADAPT (Funded by New York City Dept. of Health" with the theme AIDS is a death sentence) that are probably from the 1984/1985 period. Oversized "Brainstorming" charts have been moved to this folder from the San Francisco AIDS Foundation's Education - Planning folder.